const OS = [
    {
        question: "What is bootstrapping called?",
        options:[ "Cold boot", "Cold hot boot", "Cold hot strap", "Hot boot"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "If the page size increases, the internal fragmentation is also _____",
        options:[ "Decreases", "Increases", "Remains constant", "None of the above"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Where are placed the list of processes that are prepared to be executed and waiting?",
        options:[ "Job queue", "Ready queue", "Execution queue", "Process queue"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following does not interrupt the running process?",
        options:[ "Time interrupt", "Device", "Power failure", "Scheduler process"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Who provides the interface to access the services of the operating system?",
        options:[ "API", "System call", "Library", "Assembly instruction"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Banker's algorithm is used?",
        options:[ "To prevent deadlock", "For deadlock recovery", "To solve the deadlock", "None of these"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "BIOS is used?",
        options:[ "By operating system", "By compiler", "By interpreter", "By application software"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Aging is",
        options:[ "Keeping track of cache contents.", "Keeping track of what pages are currently residing in the memory.", "Keeping track of how many times a given page is referenced", "Increasing the priority of jobs to ensure termination in finite time"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following systems software does the job of merging the records from two files into one?",
        options:[ "Security software", "Utility program", "Networking software", "Documentation system"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following types of OS is non-interactive?",
        options:[ "Multitasking OS", "Multi-user OS", "BAtch processing OS", "Multiprogramming OS"],
        answer: 3
    }
];

export default OS;